So we begin and
now it
seems we have begun frantically there is no room
yes
he says
I will follow the teachings of the youths
315 themes yes and
he says
youths means this ancient word
from ancient books the ancient name for a teacher
means a holder the one who holds you in
his hands and I usually it is used
for teachers of the highest lamas and
this Yong Sen was a teacher of even
higher lamas and
he is famous by the way his
image
he is famous for having
written a huge book of about 2000
pages
these are biographies of teachers of lama rim from the very
beginning
we started with the biography of darma thirty
zigzags all this was received from him and it is
quite difficult to get correct
incorrect biographies of ancient lamas
because it was two thousand years ago it is
like getting the
geography of Jesus but we continue to search
and research
he lived somewhere
fifteen centuries ago and this is a very
valuable book we found and about 5 years
ago and he says
I think
you should
study
bodhichitta first and
then he
says that the right place to study
absolute bodhichitta will be where the
structure during before when
you get  up to 6 perfections
up to 6
when you get to discussing the
perfection of wisdom this is the sixth
perfection and this is where it is
necessary to teach
absolutely Abbott teacher and then our
author on Bank Rinpoche our author says
and I will do it like this and we will
study his
thoughts
on the absolute but he readings in about
2 years we have
already studied some part
11 years ago but we will
do it again don't worry
when you study the
perfection of wisdom then
you need to study the absolute bodhichitta
and
this means that now he will go to
vodka reading
what does it mean to desire to achieve
enlightenment for the sake of all living beings that is
the desire to wander through all the planets at once and
he says something really
cool here he says if we are going to
consider
ordinary bodhichitta why don't we
explore how Buddha achieved
bodhichitta how Lord Bodro Gautama
Shakyamuni how he developed his vodka that
is two stories and today we have just the
time for a story today I will tell you
two stories
grandfather will tell you two stories about
how
Buddha himself,
how he attained bodhichitta, and
I got these stories for you
because
we have a database of John
Brady's texts, and
they already
completed all the books from India somewhere around
1999. It took about 20 years, but
there are many thousands of books there, and when we need to find a
story, we go to this
repository, and
this is it. And the fact that we came up with the idea of ​​collecting everything
in one place still works
despite all the years that have passed, and you
can find a story from it in one second.
This data repository is programmed in a
special way. We never
actually updated it for computers, this is an
unheard-of fact.
Whatever it is,
then something else happens. The
first story
is found in two different sutras, but it is the
same story.
We translated one of these days, and it is
called all kinds of karma.
We worked on it for five years
during mixed nut classes, and we
completed this work, and the
story from this book.
Some of you have heard this book,
heard these stories,
the story of the ship,
we brought this entire sutra in its entirety, and there
is an ancient pyramid.
[music]
in Indonesia in Bali
sorry in Sumatra but in any case
there are ancient pyramids in the jungle which
a Dane found after he visited
this country and
so they found this pyramid and
they cleared it of Jun Ki it
seems
15,000
[music]
stories carved on stones
you know and
they made a special system of pipes so
that the water in the jungle after heavy rains
never flowed through these inscriptions
so that these inscriptions did not disappear and you
can still see all these panels after a
thousand years they will it is really
incredible
we went there
me and the doctor you
taught that and we studied all these
panels and walls
we translated many of these stories and
subsequently Doctor Wu returned to this
place with his students and they found
another level of these panels which
were in the depths because the pyramid was
collapsing it cannot be maybe the
pyramid collapsed a hundred years
ago and the
bottom row of
these panels was covered the
entire bottom level was covered so
that the pyramid would not collapse and it
worked but people did not  They removed the bricks from
this lower level and
then one of the famous
photographers
took a picture of this perch of
bricks and
they removed it and saw this row of
inscriptions and this row just
contained the story of how the lord allegedly
found bodhichitta and we had a team,
we have a team from Guadalajara, his
wife took a
picture of each panel of the inscription, it
took her about a year, he had
300 panels to copy
each language and
even if you take a photo of this panel, it is
impossible to make it out later, so she
had to
redraw everything and I am very happy to show
you one of these panels, here it is and this is an
actual drawing,
the length of her team took these inscriptions and
made drawings and
we added these drawings to the sutra and the sutra
tells this story and so why is there a
boat here and we remember that everything
happens a thousand years ago,
tell us what
ships and boats looked like at that time,
probably the
boat on which the lord of the office sailed in
order to find bodhichitta could
see such things, so let's get started
and
I will read the whole story from the sutra, here it
begins, so let's start here  Let
's start from this place and
so we will now do such a sightseeing
tour for this it took 11
years.
Team, can you please find gumball 1 liter n
bo o space eloy and so let's
look at
flounder soup and
so we read the sutra. It may take
several classes. This is a long review and I will
find an image for you
during the break between classes. I will find it for you
in my free time. Then, according to
someone's, and therefore from the biographies of
saints, both for free.
9 a book and
this is mentioned in our la times.
Mrin says that
now, guys, it's time for you to turn
to the history of the house. Puma zama means
friendly and
Sanskrit for this is mythro and
puma means daughter and
this woman named Maya trakami k and this is the
story
of how Lord Budu first found some kind of
bodhichitta under hichet at sweet sleep this
story of Maitri cognac
you can call it mythro in a short
version
in mixed nuts we translated this
story this part from the morning and this is part of the
whole book and the
whole from the morning is dedicated to the house dedicated to
feed this book karma  and this is
incredible all the
possible karma that you can only
imagine if you do this you will
get this book of rules of food and this one there
were two Austrians whom I met 8
years ago they asked me where I lived there is a
book that is there so that
all the rules of food are clear you do
this you get what and I said yes there are
two books and 1 this story of peacocks
author and
this from morning which is called all types of
karma and I said if you sponsor the translation
then I
will teach the translators and we will translate and for 6
years already these two Austrians have been sponsoring the
translation of this book and
[music]
sage do the translation in we have almost
finished it we have already finished the translation this
from morning it is incredible
yes and their plant or is it necessary and Norbert
don't forget guys yes
this is my job remind about
the donations of the
kings of this land came to listen to the
teachings of Lord Buddha yes I will now
speak a little slower and
all his great minions came to
listen
also came all the ministers and rich people
and
all the
guardians of the palace and everyone who was in the
palace  They also came and
all the merchants of the city came to
listen,
all the captains of all the ships came and
also the DVD, you came to this teaching, what is this
word and
all the nagas, yes, all the dragons, real
dragons, everyone came and the
spirit creatures also came, it sounds
a bit like the Lord of the Rings already and
all the deities came to Dan and the
cities also looked in on
them, whose is this a funny name for
ghosts, ghosts,
but no one, people, or what is this anyway,
and in fact, they look very
strange with an owl's head, that's what they are called, what is
this anyway,
tell me, someone's meme, what was it, what did it
mean, tales, fat people are
hungry ghosts,
they came to the lord, and showed their
respect,
breaking here means respect, they
showed respect,
rim eyes means that they saluted,
these are all synonyms and they made a chupa llama
miracle, they made an offering,
all these virgins, nagas,
dragons, spirits,
this is what they had musicians,
all these gods, cities,
all those who are who are they and
they all made offerings to the lord, will,
they presented to the lord  There will be
robes,
I think yes, most monks want a
test. They brought a plate of fruit and
then a new mattress. This is a typical
attitude for a monk in ancient times.
They brought
medicines.
They came to study.
Perhaps it was near the blister of power.
This is a famous city near which a
diamond cutter also studied.
I was there. This
city was found and discovered and
dug deep underground. They
found it thanks to
Drava Logu, an ancient Chinese master
who traveled through this
land.
He
wrote that if you want to get to
weaknesses from Kathmandu, you need to
travel 3-4 thousand or something.
I was in this place. It really is
beautiful. I will
exhibit this. I
was also in the Jetavana garden. The garden of Prince
Jed,
which was created not by open. Yes, yes, and
this is the guy who
got more pleasure from
feeding the homeless. And
this is a very interesting point. The
diamond cutter was taught
because a businessman and politician
made it possible. This is a wonderful
story.
It did not happen thanks to the monks
in the gardens that were donated. It is uncomfortable. Yes, yes.
he
said i would like to purchase this so that the lord of the
house can teach
and he
said cover the grass with diamonds
until i can no longer see the
ground lift it up and it was a road for the
teacher great true and
then the buddha said to
the monks and all these beings sitting in
this garden
all the monks and other people here
if
there is
any household in which
children respect and pay homage to
their
father and mother
who gave them life everything they
need
who present a gift and who serve
their parents
then
this household is
blessed
where children respect their parents
take care of
them
why is it so
your parents are
like gods
they are so important like gods
any household where children
respect their parents and
make offerings to them and
serve them in old age
those people who care about their parents will find teachers
will find their spiritual teachers why is this so
because in some sense this is
some kind of what we call it this is the magic of
help magic
there is a certain resonance a
resonance arises in reality those who care about
their parents
find spiritual teachers
this is a certain cosmic resonance
between  to take care of parents and
find a teacher
any household in which children
take care of their parents make
an offering to
their parents serve their parents
these households are
worthy of our respect deserve
our respect why is this so
because their karmic status
in karmic status in your parents are
equal to your teachers what you do
for your parents you do for budo
it is similar and korma
any household in which children
take care of parents and
their house is filled with warmth and the house is
filled in the house there is warmth
this house and not just a building
those people who take care of their
parents is really a real
home not just a building there is warmth in it
because your parents are similar
your parents this is what makes
creates the difference between a house and just a
building
if in some house children take care of
their parents they have contact
if parents
they have something important contact
because karmically
your parents are equal to
tantric deities
yes
when I said all this
he continued and said it
seems
[music]
Pinocchio Baba
Yaga
on Senators Gallagher and it
won't work out he created a whole poem yes
it's quite long  poem can you have it 5
all day you will have a great life
if you take care of your parents and
show respect and
when the Buddha finished his statement
then the Buddha said and if you have questions
let's do a question and
answer session anyone doubts
[music]
question my words
I cut off all of you and all your doubts
ask questions and
someone said oh wow this is incredible
never heard such a teaching that
parents are like tantric gods this is
really incredible
[music]
soueast and bureau and so who is the Buddha so
who is talking anyway lord well yes
who is this dish a
person who no longer desires a
person who no longer has anger and
rage no more
ignorance no
more birth aging no more
illness no more death and
by the way these words were taken from morning
which translates supping
this is from morning
[music]
12 and
this person no longer has a reason to be
sad they no longer have any
physical or mental suffering
they have overcome everything they
no longer have any mistakes and bad
deeds
they are human  who knows it all is
really possible
they know everything in the universe
they already possessed all the knowledge in the
universe
the fact
that the guy who knows everything in the
universe
tells you that it would be good to respect
you and their parents why do you think it's worth it
and it's not great incredible this is what the Buddha says a long time ago
before I became fashionable I was a
simple person I had desires I had
anger I had
ignorance and
I was locked in the wheel of life
I was a victim of aging
I also got sick and from
time to time I died
I also had problems and
I also asked questions and I
also complained I am very nice about all this
I was also subject to pain experienced
and I experienced sadness and I did the
right things in my life and
I was completely shackled completely
shackled by all this and
one day I made a mistake those days and
I come and hurt my mother a little
I harmed my mother a little and because of
this I endured incredible
suffering
but I also showed respect to my mother
and
from this I received an incredible
blessing bliss do
you want to hear this story asked the
Buddha and they said yes and he answered
I will teach you if you  promise not to forget
this until tomorrow and
by the way, in every comment,
in every time 3 promises are mentioned further,
I promise not and
I promise not to be an inverted cup, I
promised to be open to these teachings, I
promise not
from tea and coffee,
I promise not to mix these new trends
with what I learned in yoga class and I
promise not and I promise not to
leak, which means that I
promise not to forget about what minib
teaches me and now he will tell us a
story
that's how all sutras begin, he says
let me tell you a story a long time ago there
was a city called
Varanasi and the
ancient name of the city is Varanasi,
actually,
I lived there for some time if you go there I
remember
I was in a small temple and
some businessman was sitting next to me and he
said sir, I'll tell you something now
Varanasi
is a very old city 5000 years old I said
yes I know and
when you
cross the
borders of our city you are in
another universe of the game yes I believe you the
ancient name of this city  braids,
we are already
in this very old place and
Buddha lived there before becoming Buddha
and gaining enlightenment and
there was a ship captain named micro
which means
friendly
loving mythro
he was very
prosperous and rich he had a lot of
cool things
ion was very
fond of things and
his
well-being could compete with
the competition of the god of well-being cpa
given
he was afraid that
his family line
would end and
for this he got himself a wife and
he spent time with her this is
ancient ancient chemistry in order to
change sexual relations and
this means that they had children of course and
they had sons
because they had a good time
they had sons and
in India son is all
we have an operator who enters text and
he had nine daughters in a row he did
not stop and finally he had a
son then he stopped that is why
there is still a lot of ignorance
shiva
boys who are boys and continued to
die I do
n't know what the end means but it seems that
someone read his future in the palm of his hand
before  I read the lines on his palm and
predicted the future.
I have a lot of money,
but I don't have a son
and I don't have daughters either.
So after I die,
since I don't have children, the
government will take all my property
after my death.
This also happens in Arizona. He
said this and tried to comprehend it.
Then someone gave him good advice.
It's a long story. Do you mind? Yes, well,
this is history time. We may need
several lessons. Team. And
someone told him, we have something for you. I
advise you.
If you suddenly have a boy again,
give him a
girl's name. If you have a son,
give him a female name. And
by the way, this is when I was in Mongolia.
If people had miscarriages,
then a child was born
and you put it in a large
vessel and covered it and
held it for three days. You did this
secretly. And
everyone said that the child died. Yes, it's
very sad. And
they hoped that evil spirits
would be deceived. Yes, the child died, and
in fact, the child was in the
largest pot in your house. And here
the idea is the same. If you suddenly have a
baby again, name him.  female
name and
then the demons that cause
illness will be deceived
because the son can continue your mouth,
so I'll try this way
he offered prayers to all the Hindu gods
he offered many prayers to all
possible gods
they thought that he would have a child again
if
this is similar to the Indian and Indian dream
if you succeed in this trick then your
children will have another 1000 descendants
but this is a really long story
then they move on to a description of how
to catch a spirit in a room and
this description was then placed in both
darma want to hear it exactly yes
probably
I really don't like
moving parts and sutras
if parents
sexually desire each other
if umate is menstruating
then there is a
spirit nearby it will appear
if all these 3 conditions are met and
the desire of the father and mother of
menstruation and the proximity of the spirit of Bordeaux
then you will have a child then the child will appear will appear
in semolina and
in fact there
was a spirit traveling through Bordeaux and he
approached his wife and they
had sex with him the wife was
menstruating and
there is an interesting point about the spirit of Bordeaux
They have the karma of being able to pass
through walls,
but when they penetrate the
walls of the uterus, they cannot get
out, they are trapped there, and this is the
traditional explanation. Both darmas
have the karma of not being able to get back out
of the uterus.
One click if you know
[music]
then you can almost 5 signs of a
woman's uterus. You can tell without an ultrasound whether
a boy or a girl will be born.
If the child is born a boy, then he
most likely lies on the right side of the
uterus. I don't know if this is true, but
if a girl is born, then
they are more often turned to the left side of the
mother's body.
After all these descriptions of how
to get pregnant, and everyone was happy, and
then
they tried to do all this, and his
wife said, "Jova," that this is "Jova Lord,"
this is an aristocratic address to a husband, "
Lord," she turned to her husband, "I
think I have a child, I'm pregnant," and
[music]
the boy looks, and the child looks to the
right, I'm sure it's a boy,
and
he was very happy, I was
hoping for a boy all these
years, and please,
let this child call,
let nothing bad happen to him,
and let him serve his father with pleasure,
let him  he is well taken care of and
may he also have the food of
well-being and wealth and
may he continue my family line for
many, many years
after his parents
die may he continue to make
offerings to Rome to
show honor died himself
[music]
once he does
so in two minutes
in two minutes I will make announcements and
then in the second lesson I will continue to
tell the story and
he offered all these
prayers and that his son should  wives to
commit after his death and
then he took care of his wife and so that
she would not
freeze, he covered her with ideals
every time when I was hot, he blew a
fan on her, he had doctors nearby and
[music]
he did not allow her to eat spicy
Mexican food there is a tradition baba
darme that a woman
should not eat too spicy food when
she is pregnant because the child is very
sensitive
not too sour and too hot and too spicy
and
also not too salty and also
not too sweet and
not too
spiced
not too much
they
[music]
prepared all this food
prepared beautiful clothes for the child
[music]
this can be skipped and
they did not make any loud
unpleasant noise in the house and
so 8 months passed 9 months a
boy was born
very healthy and
very handsome it was nice to look at him
handsome with a beautiful complexion with a
beautifully shaped skull with nice
beautiful hands and a
prominent forehead
with a long nose, excuse me but a
beautiful nose
with beautiful lips
all his limbs  The arms, legs, fingers,
and toes were absolutely beautiful.
You know, when a child is born, parents
immediately begin to count their fingers
and toes, and
then the moment came to name the child.
Give him a name.
Don't forget
what
everyone said. The relatives said, don't
forget to give him a female name, and
they named him themselves. Puma,
mythro, cognac,
father, it was mythro, which meant
daughter, maitri.
If you wanted to name mythro,
how do you know what a
name you can name both a boy and
a girl? You could use the ending -aya in
Sanskrit.
You could call mythro maitri
if you wanted to achieve the same effect.
That's why
we translated this sutra.
Seiji, his wife, had a child,
and they decided to name him maitri.
Look at that.
Yesterday, I danced at the Lavra teaching, it's
cool, and
this one will definitely have some special
level of experience in the next one.